KATARINA OREMO

UI/UX DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

Hello!

My name is Katarina and I am a 23 year old UI/UX freelance designer. I am a passionate creative who grew up in Scandinavia and South East Asia, which makes my designs a combination of warmth with minimalism and modernity with functionality. I am currently based in Sydney, Australia, but working remotely gives me the freedom to take on projects from just about anywhere.

CONTACT DETAILS



+61 0432 235 890



katarinaaormeo@gmail.com



https://www.behance.net/katarinaailin

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry

UI Design

2021-Present

Alphacrucis University College

Theology

2022 -Present

Republic Polytechnic

UX Design 2017-2020

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bergenhus Barneskole

Primary school Substitute Teacher 2021 - 2022 Norway

Fru Blom DesignStudio

Store employee Aug 2020 - Apr 2021 Norway

Dezign Format

UI and Creative Designer 2019 - 2020 Singapore

SKILL

- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Illustrator
- Photoshop
- SketchUp